bandolierstyle.com 2018-08-16

# Privacy Policy | Bandolier | bandolierstyle.com

**EUROPEAN UNION PRIVACY POLICY** (please scroll further down for US PRIVACY POLICY)

1.      Introduction

Bandolier ( **"Company"**  or **  "We"**) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy applies where We are acting as a data controller with respect to the personal data of our website visitors, in which we determine the purposes and means of processing that personal data.

We are the data controller for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), other data protection laws applicable in Member states of the European Union and other provisions related to data protection. Our contact information is:

Bandolier

137 N Larchmont Ave., #221  
Los Angeles, CA 90048  
Phone:  800.983.6589  
Email: info@bandolierstyle.com  
Website: [www.bandolierstyle.com](http://www.bandolierstyle.com/)

2.      How we use your personal data

2.1    In this Section 2 we have set out:

(a)    the general categories of personal data that we may process;  
(b)    the purposes for which we may process personal data; and  
(c)    the legal bases of the processing.

2.2    We may process data about your use of our website and services (" **usage data** "). The usage data may include your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, as well as information about the timing, frequency and pattern of your service use. The source of the usage data is our analytics tracking system. This usage data may be processed [for the purposes of analyzing the use of the website and services. The legal basis for this processing is our interest in monitoring and improving our website and services.

2.3    We may process your account data (" **account data** "). The account data may include your name, email address, home, postal or other physical address, title, gender, occupation, industry, or personal interests, and other personal information necessary or useful to provide a product or service that you have provided to Us. The account data may be processed for the purposes of operating our website, providing our services, ensuring and communicating with you. The legal basis for this processing is performance of a contract between you and Us and the proper administration of our website and business.

2.4    We may process information that you post for publication on our website (" **publication data** "). The publication data may be processed for the purposes of enabling such publication and administering Our website and services. The legal basis for this processing is Our interest in the proper administration of our website and business.

2.6    We may process information relating to transactions, including purchases of goods, that you enter into with Us through our website (" **transaction data** "). The transaction data may include your contact details, your credit card or other form of payment details and the transaction details. The transaction data may be processed for the purpose of supplying the purchased goods and services and keeping proper records of those transactions. The legal basis for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and Us and our interest in the proper administration of Our website and business.

2.7    We may process information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters (" **notification data** "). The notification data may be processed for the purposes of sending you the relevant notifications and/or newsletters. The legal basis for this processing is your consent to receive such communications.

2.8    We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interest in the protection and assertion of our legal rights, your legal rights and the legal rights of others.

2.9    We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, or obtaining professional advice. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interest in the proper protection of our business against risks.

2.10  In addition to the specific purposes for which we may process your personal data set out in this Section 2, we may also process any of your personal data where such processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

3.      Providing your personal data to others

3.1    We may disclose your personal data to our insurers and/or professional advisers insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, obtaining professional advice, or the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.

3.2    We may disclose name, address and credit card or other payment information to the third-party service provider authorize.net for processing of payment, in order to consummate a contractual transaction for the purchase of goods and fulfill your order. This third-party provider is not authorized or permitted to use personal information for any other reason other than those pertaining to processing order transactions. You can find information about the payment services providers' privacy policies and practices at _<https://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/> _

3.3    We may disclose name and delivery address information to third parties for delivering specific products to you (such as delivery companies and other affiliates) in order to fulfill Our contractual requirements pursuant to a purchase of Our goods. In such cases, your information is not retained by these third parties or used by these companies for any secondary reasons.

3.4    In addition to the specific disclosures of personal data set out in this Section 3, We may disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person. We may also disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.

4.      International transfers of your personal data

4.1    In this Section 4, we provide information about the circumstances in which your personal data may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA).

4.2    We are a U.S. company located in Los Angeles, California. The European Commission has made an "adequacy decision" with respect to the data protection laws of each of the U.S. Transfers to the U.S. will be protected by appropriate safeguards, namely, the EU-US Privacy Shield, information about which can be obtained at: <https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/eu-us-privacy-shield_en>. The hosting facilities for our website are situated in the U.S. as well.

5.      Retaining and deleting personal data

5.1    This Section 5 sets out Our data retention policies and procedure, which are designed to help ensure that We comply with our legal obligations in relation to the retention and deletion of personal data.

5.2    Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.

5.3    The period of storage for which We will retain your personal data is the respective statutory retention period. After expiration of that period, the corresponding data is routinely deleted, as long as it is no longer necessary for the fulfillment of the contract or the initiation of a contract.

5.4    Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section 5, we may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

6.      Amendments

6.1    We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.

6.2    You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are agreeable to any changes to this policy.

7.      Your rights

7.1    In this Section 7, We have summarized the rights that you have under data protection law. Some of the rights are complex, and not all of the details have been included in Our summaries. Accordingly, you should read the relevant laws and guidance from the regulatory authorities for a full explanation of these rights.

7.2    Your principal rights under data protection law are:

(a)    the right to access;  
(b)    the right to rectification;  
(c)    the right to erasure;  
(d)    the right to restrict processing;  
(e)    the right to object to processing;  
(f)    the right to data portability;  
(g)    the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and  
(h)    the right to withdraw consent.

7.3    You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not We process your personal data and, where We do, access to the personal data, together with certain additional information. That additional information includes details of the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data. Providing the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data. The first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be subject to a reasonable fee.

7.4    You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.

7.5    In some circumstances you have the right to the erasure of your personal data without undue delay. Those circumstances include: the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed; or you withdraw consent to consent-based processing. However, there are exclusions of the right to erasure. The general exclusions include where processing is necessary: for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information; for compliance with a legal obligation; or for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.

7.6    In some circumstances you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. Those circumstances are: you contest the accuracy of the personal data; processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; We no longer need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require personal data for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; and you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection. Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your personal data. However, we will only otherwise process it: with your consent; for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or for reasons of important public interest.

7.7    You have the right to object to Our processing of your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the legal basis for the processing is that the processing is necessary for: the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of any official authority vested in Us; or the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, We will cease to process the personal information unless We can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.

7.8    You have the right to object to Our processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you make such an objection, We will cease to process your personal data for this purpose.

7.9    To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal data is:

(a)    consent; or

(b)    that the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are party or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract,

        and such processing is carried out by automated means, you have the right to receive your personal data from Us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. However, this right does not apply where it would adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.

7.10  If you consider that Our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your habitual residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.

7.11  To the extent that the legal basis for Our processing of your personal information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal.

8.      About cookies

8.1    A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.

8.2    Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.

8.3    Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

9.      Cookies that we use

9.1    We may use cookies for the following purposes:

(a)    authentication - we use cookies to identify you when you visit our website and as you navigate our website;  
(b)    status - we use cookies to help us to determine if you are logged into our website;  
(c)    personalization - we use cookies to store information about your preferences and to personalize the website for you;  
(d)    security - we use cookies as an element of the security measures used to protect user accounts, including preventing fraudulent  
use of login credentials, and to protect our website and services generally;  
(e)    advertising - we use cookies to help us to display advertisements that will be relevant to you;  
(f)    analysis - we use cookies to help us to analyze the use and performance of our website and services; and  
(g)    cookie consent - we use cookies to store your preferences in relation to the use of cookies more generally.

10.    Cookies used by our service providers

10.1  Our service providers use cookies and those cookies may be stored on your computer when you visit our website.

10.2  We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google's privacy policy is available at: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>. 

10.3  We publish Google AdSense interest-based advertisements on our website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behavior on Our website and on other websites across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the AdSense partner network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative's multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you may wish to consider using the Google browser plug-ins available at: <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996>. 

\---------------------------

**US PRIVACY POLICY**

Introduction

Bandolier ( **"Company"** or **"We"** ) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website bandolierstyle.com (our "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy, as it may change from time to time.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website.
  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
  * Through mobile and desktop applications you may download from this Website, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website.
  * When you interact with any of our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

Personal information means any information that is related to an identified person, or that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to: first and last name; email address; a home, postal or other physical address or other contact information; title, gender, occupation, industry, or personal interests; and other personal information necessary or useful to provide a product or service that you have requested. The types of personal information we collect and what we do with that information are listed below.

Domain Name and IP Address

  * We collect the domain names and IP addresses of our visitors for statistical purposes, in order to measure use, to improve the content or responsiveness of our site or to customize the content or layout of the site for the individual visitor. We do not disclose this information to third parties. We may also aggregate information relating to our visitors' traffic patterns from the data that we collect and retain concerning the IP addresses and domain names of our visitors, and we may divulge such aggregate information about our users with third parties such as our business partners, distributors, and service and support providers.
  * You may visit our Website anonymously if you wish, by using appropriate software or webservices available from or through third parties.

Log Files

  * We maintain a log file of all actions that are initiated or facilitated using our Website in order to capture, record and store data concerning the transaction. Access to this data is restricted to internal usage by authorized Bandolier employees who administer our network and website.

E-Mail Address

  * You should know that e-mail is not necessarily secure against all forms of interception. If your communication includes sensitive information about you and you would prefer not to transmit this information in this fashion, please contact us by mail or telephone rather than e-mail. See the "Contact" section below for this information.
  * We collect e-mail addresses that are volunteered by the visitor, from e-mail messages addressed to our company or its employees or provided by the visitor when placing an order on the site.
  * We use the e-mail addresses for marketing purposes and to inform those interested in our products about events, products, services or other items of interest. Additionally, we use the e-mail addresses to notify visitors about recent updates to our website, to provide product or service news notifications or to send newsletters and promotions. We also use the e-mail addresses to process orders for products, services, brochures and other written materials, to respond to customer questions, to provide customer service and to inquire as to customer satisfaction and feedback.
  * You may opt-out of receiving the promotional or marketing e-mails at any time by choosing to unsubscribe to promotional or marketing e-mails via the attached link to do so in such e-mails. If you choose to opt-out of receiving such e-mails, Bandolier’s records will be updated within ten days of receipt of your request. These opt-out procedures will not be available for e-mails that are necessary to provide confirmation of a completed transaction (such as a purchase or change in the visitor's user profile).

Credit Card Information

  * We collect credit card and billing information from visitors who make purchases from our online store. We use this information to bill the customer for product purchases. Credit card data will not be saved.
  * Collection and processing of credit cards is performed by the third-party service provider authorize.net. This third party provider is not authorized or permitted to use personal information for any other reason other than those pertaining to processing order transactions.

Other Personal Information

  * When you place an order with our site, you provide other personal information including your name, mailing address, billing address and phone number. This information is used to process orders placed on our online store and to facilitate customer service and the delivery of products you have ordered. Your mailing address and telephone number may be used to contact you about orders placed on-line or to provide information that you have requested.
  * If you post reviews or comments on the bandolierstyle.com site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in comments on our site.

**Personal Information Released to Outside Parties**

Any information that you provide to us will be used for our purposes only. Except as specified in this Policy, your information will not be shared with individuals outside the employ of Bandolier (TM) or with other companies.

In some instances we may provide your name and delivery address to third parties that we use for delivering specific products to you (such as delivery companies and other affiliates). The process of fulfilling orders placed via the online store may also require Bandolier to share your information with other third parties such as automated data processors and credit card processors. In such cases, your information is not retained by these third parties or used by these companies for any secondary reasons.

Bandolier complies with applicable law and legal obligations to respond to governmental, law enforcement and court requests for personal information and other information and data about our visitors and their transactions. Bandolier’s legal counsel may access and use your personal information and other information or data in the event of a dispute, in response to legal process or law enforcement inquiries, abuse of our website, or violation of our Terms of Service Policy.

We may also disclose information if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Bandolier, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Cookies**

A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. To use portions of Bandolier's Website you must set your browser to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

Bandolier may use session cookies. These cookies may be used for a variety of reasons such as to keep track of items in your shopping cart. This information is encrypted and stored in a cookie during that session. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website.  Some of our business partners (e.g., service providers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.bandolierstyle.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertiser.

**Editing Your Personal Profile**

We provide a means to create a personal account or profile of personal information when you register on the retail section of our site. We realize that your personal information, including your name and e-mail address, is subject to change. To the extent that you provide us with personal information, we wish to maintain its accuracy. To change or delete the information in your personal account, by selecting My Account on our site and following the prompts to edit your profile. Any submitted changes to your account will occur within seven business days.

**Data Security**

Your store account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. We safeguard the security of the data you send us with certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We have taken reasonable precautions to protect against misuse, theft, loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of your personal information. Additionally, we use industry-standard 128-Bit SSL Encryption to enhance the security of data transmissions.

While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. We suggest that you change your passwords often, that your passwords include a combination of letters and numbers, and that you make certain that you are using a secure browser. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

**Children's Privacy**

We do not structure our website to attract children. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect information from anyone who is age 13 and under.

**Third Party Sites**

Our Website contains links to other sites. When you click on one of these links you are being transferred to a website operated by someone other than Incase, and the operator of that website may have a different privacy policy. Bandolier does not share your personal information with these websites and is not responsible for their individual privacy practices. We encourage you to investigate the privacy policies of these operators.

**Future Changes**

By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this Privacy Policy and to our Terms and Conditions. Bandolier may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page or by notice on our homepage, so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will post a notice on this page for thirty (30) calendar days prior to the implementation of any material changes to this Privacy Policy. Such notice will provide information as to how you may remove your information from our database should you so desire.

**Contact**

To contact Bandolier please email info@bandolierstyle.com.
